HARMONIE KRIEGER: So, now we're here on a red carpet makeover and we're going into evening dresses.
So, we have Patricia, our beautiful model, and what I chose for her was a very sleek black dress, and the top is all sequined, so it brings out your upper body, 'cause she has bone structure, muscles.
And then, it just flares down at the leg where you see a little bit leg, but not too much.
And I love this look because black is always the sexiest color.
So, how do you feel in this dress, do you like it?
PATRICIA: I feel fabulous.
I love it.
HARMONIE KRIEGER: Good.
Now, this is for sure a red carpet dress.
Now, the makeover is not just for the red carpet.
It's for any special event.
So, it could be for a wedding.
I mean I wear this for a wedding, a cocktail party, anything that's special in your life.
This is another variation and this is called a halter top.
And I like this because it kinda just lifts me up a little bit too, and blue because I always like to add a little bit of color.
So, we have a little bit of a different kind of dress.
This is a party dress and this is more a sexy, sleek, red carpet dress.
So, you're going to pick the gown that's the best for you.
Now, everybody has different shapes and sizes.
It's really hard picking a dress, isn't it?
PATRICIA: Yes.
But I think you did an awesome job and you do look fabulous.
HARMONIE KRIEGER: Thank you, and I love that on you.
PATRICIA: Yes.
HARMONIE KRIEGER: So, basically it's what's flattering to your own body.
Now, always get a second and third opinion because the dress that you may like might not be the one that looks best on you.
So take a friend, take a relative, and take some pictures, because you always want to see how you look in the camera before you put the dress on.